//Questions taken from Assessment from Trilogy Bootcamps
var questions = [
{
    question: "Inside the HTML document, where do you place your JavaScript code?",
    choice1: "Inside the <head> element",
    choice2: "Inside the <script> element",
    choice3: "Inside the <link> element", 
    choice4: "In the <footer> element",
    answer: 2
},
{
    question: "What operator is used to assign a value to a declared variable?",
    choice1: "Question mark (?)", 
    choice2: "Colon (:)", 
    choice3: "Equal sign (=)", 
    choice4: "Double-equal (==)",
    answer: 3
},

{
    question: "What are the six primitive data types in JavaScript?",
    choice1: "string, num, falsy, bigInt, symbol, undefined",
    choice2: "sentence, int, truthy, bigInt, symbol, undefined", 
    choice3: "string, number, boolean, bigInt, symbol, undefined", 
    choice4: "sentence, float, data, bigInt, symbol, undefined",
    answer: 3
},

{
    question: "How do we declare a conditional statement in JavaScript?",
    choice1: "if...else", 
    choice2: "difference...between", 
    choice3: "for loop", 
    choice4: "while loop",
    answer: 1
},

{
    question: "From the given array which index is the letter 'b' on? ['a', 'b', 'c', 'd']",
    choice1: "0", 
    choice2: "1", 
    choice3: "2",
    choice4: "3",
    answer: 2
},

{
    question: "What are the two types of scope JavaScript uses?",
    choice1: "Outside and Inside", 
    choice2: "Abroad and Local", 
    choice3: "Surrounding and Inner", 
    choice4: "Global and Local",
    answer: 4
},

{
    question: "How do we access a value stored in an object?",
    choice1: "Period notation, Square bracket notation",
    choice2: "Dot notation, Bracket notation", 
    choice3: "Equal notation, Abstract notation", 
    choice4:"Dot notation, Curl bracket notation",
    answer: 4
},

{
    question: "What is an object method?",
    choice1: "A function associated with an object", 
    choice2: "A function that takes an object for an argument", 
    choice3: "Keys in an object that have a number assigned to it", 
    choice4: "An array saved inside of an object",
    answer: 2
},

{
    question: "Arrays in JavaScript can be used to store ____.",
    choice1: "numbers and strings", 
    choice2: "other arrays", 
    choice3: "booleans", 
    choice4: "all of the above",
    answer: 4
  },

  {
    question: "String values must be enclosed within ____ when being assigned to variables.",
    choice1: "commas",
    choice2: "curly brackets", 
    choice3: "quotes", 
    choice4:"parentheses",
    answer: 3
  },

  {
    question: "A very useful tool used during development and debugging for printing content to the debugger is:",
    choice1: "JavaScript", 
    choice2: "terminal / bash", 
    choice3: "for loops", 
    choice4: "console.log",
    answer: 4
  },
  {
    question: "What is the type of Pop up boxes available in JavaScript?:",
    choice1: "Alert",
    choice2: "Confirm", 
    choice3: "Prompt", 
    choice4: "All the above",
    answer: 4
  }
];